<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: The Better You Get, Seems the Worse Things Are &#8211; Thursday, June 22	</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../index.html</link>
	<description>Daily Status and Progress</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 15:09:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>
		By: Debbie Pollak (daughter of Sarah Pollak)		</title>
		<link>./../index.html#comment-134</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Debbie Pollak (daughter of Sarah Pollak)]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 15:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../index.html?p=592#comment-134</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Good morning Sue,
After not being able to walk for 5 days, I finally gave into another cortisone shot in my right knee. I am trying to return to water aerobics class on Tuesday. I have missed three weeks and it is awful. i will work hard to get stronger again so I can drive out to see you again. I am so sorry that I have been unable to do this.  I had a battle with the Kaiser people because they cannot understand what &quot;living alone&quot; means. I know you understand this all too well. I finally packed my knee with ice and got to see someone to get the shot. Now I am getting better but it is only temporary.
Please do not think I have been neglecting you. YOU are very important to me and your friendship is a treasure for me. Hopefully, this week will go well and I can see you the week after this one.
I am doing my best to be stronger. Love and a huge hug, Debbie]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Good morning Sue,<br />
After not being able to walk for 5 days, I finally gave into another cortisone shot in my right knee. I am trying to return to water aerobics class on Tuesday. I have missed three weeks and it is awful. i will work hard to get stronger again so I can drive out to see you again. I am so sorry that I have been unable to do this.  I had a battle with the Kaiser people because they cannot understand what &#8220;living alone&#8221; means. I know you understand this all too well. I finally packed my knee with ice and got to see someone to get the shot. Now I am getting better but it is only temporary.<br />
Please do not think I have been neglecting you. YOU are very important to me and your friendship is a treasure for me. Hopefully, this week will go well and I can see you the week after this one.<br />
I am doing my best to be stronger. Love and a huge hug, Debbie</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
